skafeed.com 2018-12-18

# Privacy Policy | Skafeed - Fashion Blog

The privacy of our users is of upmost importance here at skafeed. This is the place to find out how we look after your privacy and what non-personally identifiable information we use to target our advertisements.

**Skafeed Privacy Statement**

Internet user privacy is of paramount importance to Skafeed. The success of our business depends upon our ability to maintain the trust of our users. Below is information regarding Skafeed’s commitment to protect the privacy of users and ensure the integrity of the Internet.

### Information collected in advertisement delivery

In the course of delivering an ad to you, skafeed does not collect any personally identifiable information about you, such as your name, address, phone number or email address. Skafeeddoes, however, use a number of different adserving solutions including ValueClick Media, Burst Media, Casale Media and Primitive Network to collect non-personally identifiable information about you, such as the server your computer is logged onto, your browser type (for example, Mozilla Firefox or Microsoft Internet Explorer), and whether you responded to the ad delivered. The non-personally identifiable information collected by Skafeed is for the purpose of targeting ads and measuring ad effectiveness on behalf of AdBalance’s advertisers.

### Third Party Advertising

We use ValueClick Media, Burst Media, Casale Media, and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://networkadvertising.org/).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).
